Hikmat Malkawi

Front End Web Developer

Front End Developer with 2 years of experience, I have a good experience in Front End JS frameworks especially Vue js and nuxt js (which I love), I also have good knowledge in other frameworks like react js and react native, and I have a good experience with the REST API's and the integration process with the front end screens, also I have the knowledge with the basic definition of the back end.

Mathematical health hea

+962788638054

Jordan

in linkedin.com/in/hikmat-malkawi/



github.com/EngHikmat

SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, C++, Python

Web Design: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, FontAwesome, Basics of Vuetify and Tailwind

Front End Frameworks: Vue JS , Nuxt Js and the basics of React JS

Work Experience

Front End Web Developer

SHIPCASH

02/2021 - 07/2022

Amman, Jordan

- I've worked on 2 real projects in my contract period as a front-end developer.
- I was responsible for implementing the UI designs I get from the Project Manager and organizing the files and routes
- · I was able to collaborate and negotiate with the backend developers, front-end developers, and project manager through meetings to come up with the best solution for any issue or to finish any common part of the tasks.
- We were organizing our work using Trello, to stay focused on tasks and get off distractions, especially on working pressure days.
- I was the leading front-end developer at the company, so I was responsible for many projects done from my side, which let me deal with many front-end frameworks, Vue Js, and Nuxt Js.
- I was able to assign tasks to the front-end and back-end entry-level developers and also explain and clarify them.

Full-Stack Web Engineer

CBM INTEGRATED SOFTWARE INC

08/2020 - 02/2021

Amman, Jordan

- I had got a month period to learn the fundamentals of web development, HTML, CSS, and bootstrap.
- I made a presentation for every concept to explain them, then created a simple project to employ what I have learned.
- Learned the first framework in my life, which was react js, hooks, and custom hooks, then I developed a simple weather App project, which was based on integrating the RestAPI I got with my react project, using a simple fetch method
- I had assigned to plan to create a simple appointments system for employees, I was responsible to create the UI and then translating them to real front-end code.
- Learned the backend side, which was based on node js, GraphQl, Sequelize, and Mysgl then learned how to create the models and tables, and applied them to my appointment project.

Education

Bachelor in Software Engineering

Jordan University Of Science and Technology 09/2014 - 09/2019

Languages

Arabic

Native

English

Intermediate